<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gonzalo Parra Alvarez</title><link>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/</link><description>Recent content on Gonzalo Parra Alvarez</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:48:02 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Web Automation with Notifications</title><link>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/projects/web-automation-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:48:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/projects/web-automation-tool/</guid><description>Overview: Python scripts to automate tasks on the browser. Useful for sites that do not have notifications or waiting lists. Goal is to avoid manual polling. Notifications on every platform thanks to an slack bot included.
Project State: In development.
Used Technologies: python for the scripts selenium as the core library to control the browser helium as an abstraction layer to interact with selenium bolt for python as the framework for the slack bot usind websocket slack API TODOs add more interactions with the slack bot.</description></item><item><title>Personal Web Presentation</title><link>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/projects/web-presentation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 10:48:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/projects/web-presentation/</guid><description>Overview: A static website to showcase projects, inititatives, learnings and fun stuff.
Project State: In development.
Used Technologies: hugo a framework for building static websites coder template for the hugo framework github actions for automated deployment. github pages for hosting on my own domain. TODOs add more projects Source: The source code can be found on my github.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/resume/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 10:48:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dev.parra-alvarez.de/resume/</guid><description>Working Experience 09/2019 - today Engineering Manager - Smart Cities, E.ON Energy Research Center, Aachen Led the architecture design and implementation of cloud-based, real-time, data-driven energy services for real state. Managed of lighthouse field project from the initiative from the German Ministry of Economics. Stats: 25 people, 5 institutions, 2 Mio. EUR. Consulted European Corporations in data-driven decision making Highlights: Project Management, Software Engineering, Data-Driven ROI calculations, Lifecycle-Assessment 09/2019 – today Consultant - Digitization and IoT Business Models, Self-Employed, Aachen Advised mid-sized companies on strategy for IoT Business Models.</description></item></channel></rss>